{"tokens": ["Saunders", ")", "River", "(", "Lawrence", "St.", "R.H.", ")", "968", "MW", "("], "ner_tags": ["I-ORG", "O", "I-ORG", "O", "I-ORG", "B-ORG", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": [")", "born", "1968", "(", "Ove", "Knausgård", "Karl"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "I-PER", "I-PER", "B-PER"]}
{"tokens": ["Atlantic", "City", ",", "Jersey", "New"], "ner_tags": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["Mary", "St.", "'s", "Church", "Catholic", "Sandusky", "(", "Ohio", ",", ")"], "ner_tags": ["I-ORG", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Shhh", "..."], "ner_tags": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Antonín", "Rýgr", "(", "1970–72", ")"], "ner_tags": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Inducted", "into", "the", "States", "United", "Hockey", "Hall", "of", "Fame", "in", "2015", "*"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "I-ORG", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["102.7"], "ner_tags": ["O"]}
{"tokens": ["*", "Highway", "px", "20", "Idaho", "State", "5"], "ner_tags": ["O", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["''", "1884", "Meyrick", "Atelocentra", ",", "''"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["'", "''", "prion", "Antarctic", "'", "'", "'"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "I-LOC", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Franco", "James", "M.F.A", "(", "."], "ner_tags": ["I-PER", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Victor", "Albert", "Prince", "Duke", "of", "Clarence", "and", "Avondale", ","], "ner_tags": ["I-PER", "I-PER", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER"]}
{"tokens": ["Away", "'", "to", "Get", "How", "with", "Murder", "'"], "ner_tags": ["I-ORG", "O", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Durrães", "e", "Tregosa"], "ner_tags": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["Brent", "Cross", "tube", "station"], "ner_tags": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["recorded", "First", "in", "the", "de", "las", "Serranía", "Quinchas", "on", "January", "17", ",", "2006", "."], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Party", "Freedom", "Civic"], "ner_tags": ["I-ORG", "I-ORG", "B-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["キイロキリガ", "—", "Xanthia", "togata", "''", "(", "Esper", ")", ",", "1788"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["*", "8", "August", "–", "Craig", "Breslow"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER"]}
{"tokens": ["He", "also", "has", "twice", "won", "the", "Senior", "Japan", "Open", "."], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "I-ORG", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Whit", "is", "Stillman", "director", "His", "grandson", "great-", "."], "ner_tags": ["B-PER", "O", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": [",", "Janaki", "]", "S.", "Balasubrahmanyam", "P.", "]"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Obituary", "of", "Juliette", "Peirce", "."], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["78", "''", "in", "Osnabrück", "."], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Girolamo", "Albani", "Gian"], "ner_tags": ["I-PER", "I-PER", "B-PER"]}
{"tokens": ["Rhinestone", "Cowboy", "''", "Weiss", "Larry", "(", "``", "-", "3:15", ")"], "ner_tags": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "I-PER", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["9", "Episode", "*", "Conlan", "Michael", "-"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "I-PER", "B-PER", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Antawn", "Jamison", "(", "28", ")"], "ner_tags": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Hauteserre", "de", "Antoine", "Dadin"], "ner_tags": ["I-PER", "I-PER", "B-PER", "I-PER"]}
{"tokens": ["de", "Champs-sur", "Château", "Marne", "-"], "ner_tags": ["I-ORG", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Secretary", "-", "General", "of", "the", "Nations", "United"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": [",", "7–5", "Carina", "Witthöft", ",", "6–3"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["CCStaClara", ":", ".", "File"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["District", "National", "Eveno-Bytantaysky"], "ner_tags": ["I-LOC", "I-LOC", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["''", "Euxoa", "centralis", "''", ")", ",", "1889", "Staudinger", "("], "ner_tags": ["O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Diocese", "of", "San", "Tuxtla", "Andrés"], "ner_tags": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["Palisades", ",", "York", "New"], "ner_tags": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["Powell", "Rosephanye", ")", "born", "1962", "("], "ner_tags": ["I-PER", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["District", "Chum", "Ta", "Bong"], "ner_tags": ["I-LOC", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["Epica", "–", "Consign", "to", "Oblivion", "'", "'"], "ner_tags": ["B-ORG", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["episodes", ")", "series", "1990", "radio", "(", "List", "of", "Flywheel", "Flywheel", "and", ",", "Shyster", ","], "ner_tags": ["I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["rivata", "''", "(", "Hübner", ",", "1813", ")", "Epirrhoe", "''"], "ner_tags": ["I-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["**", "''", "Elite", "''", "League", "Justice", ":"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "I-ORG", "O", "I-ORG", "B-ORG", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["It", "is", "found", "in", "Peru", "."], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O"]}
{"tokens": [":", "Ecuador", "**", "7", "%", "of", "the", "population"], "ner_tags": ["O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Translator", "-", "Park", ",", "Overland", "FM", "Kansas", ",", "of", "KCCV"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "I-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": [".", "Brigitte", "Mrs", "Vallée"], "ner_tags": ["O", "B-PER", "O", "I-PER"]}
{"tokens": ["Lipiny", ",", "County", "Ciechanów"], "ner_tags": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["Tatiana", "Volosozhar", "Trankov", "Maxim", "/"], "ner_tags": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "B-PER", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Raymerville", "–", "East", "Markville", "Ontario", ","], "ner_tags": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["Robert", ",", "Lord", "5th", "Maxwell", "Maxwell", "(", "1493–1546", ")"], "ner_tags": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Prince", "Rupert", "November", "1682", "of", "the", "Rhine", "1672", "15", "August", "–", "19"], "ner_tags": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Železničná", "spoločnos", "Slovensko", "ť"], "ner_tags": ["B-ORG", "O", "I-ORG", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["he", "On", "February", "6", ",", "1925", "retired", "from", "active", "duty", ".", "and", "died", "in", "Santiago", "in", "1938"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["in", "the", "2012–13", "OHL", "season", "in", "place", "last", "'s", "finished", "with", "just", "16", "wins", "The", "67", "."], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Point", "Exchange", "Internet", ")", "IXP", "("], "ner_tags": ["I-ORG", "I-ORG", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["as", "the", "single", "first", "from", "their", "2004", "album", "Everybody", "Loves", "a", "Happy", "Ending", "''", "was", "released", "It", "is", "the", "single", "first", "and", "since", "1990", "that", "features", "both", "members", "original", "Roland", "Orzabal", "Curt", "Smith", "and", "."], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Conservative", "]", "]"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Much", "of", "the", "story", "place", "takes", "in", "Flagstaff", ",", "Arizona", ",", "where", "Sgt", "."], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["''", "Invisible", "Touch", "–", "Genesis", "''"], "ner_tags": ["O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-ORG", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Librarian", "States", "United", "Senate"], "ner_tags": ["I-PER", "I-PER", "B-PER", "I-PER"]}
{"tokens": ["Live", "at", "Sin", "-é", "'", "'", "Edition", "(", "Legacy", ")"], "ner_tags": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["*", "2001", "Kimmel", "Jimmy", "Hefner", "Hugh", ",", "Roastmaster", "–"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "I-PER", "B-PER", "I-PER", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Aigle", "Noir", "AC"], "ner_tags": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Mountain", "Hathaways", "Pines", "California", ","], "ner_tags": ["I-LOC", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["Peter", "King", "T."], "ner_tags": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER"]}
{"tokens": ["Charlie", "Clouser", "–", "Nails", "Nine", "Inch"], "ner_tags": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "I-ORG", "B-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Bartholomew", "St", "church", "Former", "collegiate", "Liège", ","], "ner_tags": ["I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "B-LOC", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["District", "Zlaté", "Moravce"], "ner_tags": ["I-LOC", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["Gustav", "Franz", "Herter", "Wilhelm"], "ner_tags": ["I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "B-PER"]}
{"tokens": ["Thomasville", ",", "Missouri"], "ner_tags": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": [".", "14", "Clement", "Poitrenaud", ","], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["France", "de", "Tour", "1982"], "ner_tags": ["I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "B-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["-", "Denison", "Baron", "1st", "Pender", "John", "Pender", ","], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER"]}
{"tokens": ["''", "(", ",", "1880", "Meyrick", ")", "Glyphipterix", "iometalla", "''"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["''", ")", ",", "1789", "Esper", "(", "Zygaena", "cynarae", "''"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["''", "Super", "World", "'", "of", "Sports", "'", "'"], "ner_tags": ["O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Chananel", "ben", "Chushiel"], "ner_tags": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER"]}
{"tokens": ["Bobby", "Rush", ")", "D", "("], "ner_tags": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["'", "Legend", "of", "Hyang", "Chun", "'"], "ner_tags": ["O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["BBC", ")", "'", "Match", "Test", "Special", "(", "'"], "ner_tags": ["B-ORG", "O", "O", "I-ORG", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Bruce", "Beresford", "-", "Non", "Jew", ")", "("], "ner_tags": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["was", "released", "It", "also", "along", "with", "Studio", "2005", ",", "2005", "Server", "SQL", "Microsoft", "Visual", ",", "2006", "and", "BizTalk", "."], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "B-ORG", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Leonardo", "Solís", "Rodríguez"], "ner_tags": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER"]}
{"tokens": ["She", "on", "10", "January", "1836", "was", "born", "in", "Aldsworth", "Gloucestershire", ",", ",", "England", "."], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Kyoto", "National", "Museum", "**", ")", "production", "early", "cast", "("], "ner_tags": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["List", "of", "years", "in", "Brazil"], "ner_tags": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["it", "was", "sold", "to", "National", "Express", "who", "sold", "to", "Connex", "it", "in", "September", "2004", "In", "June", "1999", "."], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["20", "px", "Władysław", "I", "the", "Elbow-high"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER"]}
{"tokens": [",", "November", "29", "–", "15", "May", "1971", "1965", "Misawa", "AB", ",", "Japan"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["Flatnose", "xenocongrid", "eel"], "ner_tags": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["to", "run", "for", "West", "Hobart", "in", "March", "1906", "He", "resigned", ".", ",", "but", "was", "unsuccessful"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["de", "Lăpugiu", "Jos"], "ner_tags": ["I-LOC", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["Chinantec", "of", "Ozumacín"], "ner_tags": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["–", "4", "October", "*", "Drew", "Stubbs"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER"]}
{"tokens": ["16th", "Troop", "Carrier", "Squadron", ":", "attached", "November", "1954", "–", "8", "July", "1955", "14"], "ner_tags": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["File", "|", "fontannaPotop", "10-2013.jpg", "Bdg", "2", ":"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["by", "Warren", "was", "described", "It", "in", "1892", "."], "ner_tags": ["O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Varghese", "Palakkappilly", "Payyappilly"], "ner_tags": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER"]}
{"tokens": ["He", "in", "Sundridge", ",", "Ontario", "was", "born", "in", "."], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Greece", ":", "League", "Super", "1982–83"], "ner_tags": ["I-ORG", "O", "I-ORG", "B-ORG", "B-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Island", ",", "Christmas", "on", "8", "November", "1957", ",", "28", "22", "April", ",", "2", "September", "September", "11", ",", "August", ",", ",", "or", "23", "September", "1958"], "ner_tags": ["I-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Guy", "Berryman", "(", "Coldplay", ")"], "ner_tags": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Jason", "Schwartzman", "Dustin", "Hoffman", ",", "Huppert", "Isabelle", ","], "ner_tags": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "I-PER", "B-PER", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["'", "'", "Lena", "'", "Springs", "'", "''"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "I-PER", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["He", "is", "a", "former", "England", "under", "-", "21", "international", "."], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "I-ORG", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Clement", "''", "''Stromata", "of", "Alexandria", ",", "1.131.6", "."], "ner_tags": ["B-PER", "O", "O", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Rights", "Human", "Commission", "of", "Malaysia"], "ner_tags": ["I-ORG", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "elevation", "is", "3944", "feet", "above", "sea", "level", ".", "(", "1202", "m", ")"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Frédéric", "Jean", "Frenet"], "ner_tags": ["I-PER", "B-PER", "I-PER"]}
{"tokens": ["Poland", "in", "the", "Song", "Eurovision", "Contest"], "ner_tags": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["'", "Heater", "''", "Space", "'", "(", "album", ")"], "ner_tags": ["O", "I-ORG", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Thompson", "–", "International", "Speedway", "Thompson", ",", "Connecticut"], "ner_tags": ["B-ORG", "O", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "B-ORG", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["Recorded", "at", "Alberts", "Studio", ",", "London", "."], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-LOC", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Canton", "Herzegovina", "West"], "ner_tags": ["I-LOC", "I-LOC", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["Autonomous", "Ili", "Kazakh", "Prefecture"], "ner_tags": ["I-LOC", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["London", ".", "Thames", ":", "&", "Hudson", "**"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Takht", "Sri", "Hazur", "Sahib", "Nanded", ","], "ner_tags": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "B-LOC", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["]s", "]", "lifebelt", "that", "survived", "the", "sinking", "is", "on", "display", "at", "the", "War", "Imperial", "Museum", "in", "Manchester", "North"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "I-ORG", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-LOC", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Qusai", "ibn", "Manaf", "Abd", "was", "His", "father", "."], "ner_tags": ["I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["El", "Borg", "Arab", "Stadium", "Egypt", ",", "Alexandria", ","], "ner_tags": ["I-ORG", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "B-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["A", "``", "Corner", "'", "Different", "'"], "ner_tags": ["B-ORG", "O", "I-ORG", "O", "I-ORG", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["1283", ":", "The", "Dynasty", "Yuan", "claim", "possession", "of", "the", "Penghu", "Islands"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "I-ORG", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Alain", "Delon", "Carla", "Gravina", ",", "Conte", "Richard", ","], "ner_tags": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "I-PER", "B-PER", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["**", "George", "V", ",", "King", "of", "the", "United", "Kingdom", "(", "1910", "–", "1936", ")", "Monarch", "-"], "ner_tags": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Helene", "Hayman", "Baroness", ",", "Hayman"], "ner_tags": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER"]}
{"tokens": ["''", "Smith", "'", "Zadie", "'", "'", "'"], "ner_tags": ["O", "I-PER", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Glencoe", ",", "KwaZulu", "-Natal"], "ner_tags": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["''", "Polystichum", "acrostichoides", "''", "(", "Michx", "."], "ner_tags": ["O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["It", "is", "on", "the", "Campaign", "for", "Real", "Ale", "'s", "National", "Inventory", "of", "Pub", "Historic", "Interiors", "."], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["''", "You", "'re", "the", "Voice", "``"], "ner_tags": ["O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["5", "Route", "State", "York", "New"], "ner_tags": ["I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "B-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["hommes", "et", "des", ",", "frères", "des", "pères", "Des"], "ner_tags": ["I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "B-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Two", "and", "a", "Half", "Men"], "ner_tags": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["the", "area", "was", "part", "of", "Germany", "Before", "1945", "."], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["5000", "-", "meter", "(", "2015", ")", "run", "–", "14:15.61"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "I-ORG", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Sridevi", ",", "Sanjay", ",", "Dutt", "Rahul", "Roy"], "ner_tags": ["B-PER", "O", "B-PER", "O", "I-PER", "B-PER", "I-PER"]}
{"tokens": ["Miranda", "as", "the", "Singer", "Martino"], "ner_tags": ["B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "I-PER"]}
{"tokens": ["Communist", "Party", "of", "Nigeria", ")", "CPN", "("], "ner_tags": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["''", "falcula", "Chaetodon", "''", "butterflyfish", "Blackwedged", ",", "**"], "ner_tags": ["O", "I-ORG", "B-ORG", "O", "I-LOC", "B-LOC", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "first", "settlers", "arrived", "in", "the", "early", "century", "19th", "Quakers", "were", "largely", "and", "Mennonites", ",", ",", "Loyalists", "Empire", "United", "and", "who", "had", "left", "the", "United", "States", "."], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-LOC", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Republic", "of", "Ezo", "(", "1868–1869", ")"], "ner_tags": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Hul", ",", "District", "Zámky", "Nové"], "ner_tags": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["Carías", "Tiburcio", "Andino", "Tegucigalpa", "Honduras", ",", "Estadio"], "ner_tags": ["I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "B-LOC", "B-LOC", "O", "B-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Bokówka", ",", "Voivodeship", "Podlaskie"], "ner_tags": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": [".", "A.", "Robert", "Borski", ",", "Jr"], "ner_tags": ["I-PER", "I-PER", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER"]}
{"tokens": ["Perry", ",", ",", "Ohio", "County", "Fayette", "Township"], "ner_tags": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["''", "Tsardom", "'", "Feodor", "III", "–", "(", "1676–1682", ")", "of", "Russia", "''"], "ner_tags": ["O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["St", "'s", "University", ",", ")", "SGUL", "(", "of", "London", "George"], "ner_tags": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["national", "team", "Wales", "football"], "ner_tags": ["I-ORG", "I-ORG", "B-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["*", "wisent", "(", "'", "bonasus", "Bison", "'", ")"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "I-ORG", "B-ORG", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Warrandyte", ",", "Victoria", "South"], "ner_tags": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["Prochoreutis", "stellaris", "''", ")", ",", "1847", "Zeller", "(", "''"], "ner_tags": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["UEFA"], "ner_tags": ["B-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["he", "In", "1926", "was", "promoted", "to", "the", "rank", "of", "Marshal", "of", "Italy", "."], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "I-PER", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Her", "grandson", "Booth", "Francis", "-Clibborn", "Eric", "Stanley", "became", "the", "Anglican", "Bishop", "of", "Manchester", "."], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "I-PER", "O", "I-PER", "B-PER", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["It", "will", "serve", "the", "suburb", "of", "Downs", "Murrumba", "in", "the", "Bay", "Moreton", "Region", "."], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "I-ORG", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "I-LOC", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Lawrence", "of", "Rome"], "ner_tags": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "Larry", "Sanders"], "ner_tags": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["was", "on", "twice", "Coming", "as", "a", "substitute", ",", "he", "selected", "to", "start", "in", "the", "semi-final", "loss", "to", "Brazil", "."], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["–", "September", "7", "''", "Little", "Shop", "''"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Alexander", "of", "Hales", "1245", "(", ")", "died", ","], "ner_tags": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Louis", "Eppolito", "Stephen", "and", "Caracappa"], "ner_tags": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER"]}
{"tokens": ["Township", "Yale", "Valley", "County", ",", "Nebraska", ","], "ner_tags": ["I-LOC", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["''", "Slavonija", ":", "Slavonia", "''"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["(", "born", "11", "March", "1983", ")", "Steven", "Sutherland", "John"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "I-PER", "I-PER", "B-PER"]}
{"tokens": ["S.", "College", "of", "Technology", "K.", "Rangasamy"], "ner_tags": ["I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "B-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["St.", "'s", "Mary", "College", ",", "Kegalle"], "ner_tags": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Liam", "*", "Charms", "Lucky", "references", "."], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "I-PER", "B-PER", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Marcher", "Gold", "Classic", "and", "Chester", "Wrexham", ","], "ner_tags": ["I-ORG", "I-ORG", "B-ORG", "O", "B-LOC", "B-LOC", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["DRS", "-", "101.5", "MHz", ")", "60", "kW", "(", "1"], "ner_tags": ["B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["University", "of", "Minnesota", "Marvin", "Dunnette", ","], "ner_tags": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["off", "Get", "the", "Stage"], "ner_tags": ["I-ORG", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["''", "Şımarık", "–", "Tarkan", "''"], "ner_tags": ["O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-PER", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["(", "1903—", "2002", ")", "Leuven", "K.", "Stade"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "I-ORG", "B-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Patrick", "Ryan", "(", "priest", "Irish", ")"], "ner_tags": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER"]}
{"tokens": ["Image", "V02p108001", ":"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["''", "endochus", "Graphium", "''", "(", ",", "1836", "Boisduval", ")"], "ner_tags": ["O", "I-LOC", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["rider", "Circuit", "(", "Technology", ")"], "ner_tags": ["I-ORG", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Tachibana", "no", "Naramaro"], "ner_tags": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER"]}
{"tokens": ["Rajiv", "Gandhi", "Stadium", "Cricket", "International"], "ner_tags": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["in", "Turkey", "Alanya", "-"], "ner_tags": ["O", "B-LOC", "B-LOC", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["He", "was", "the", "manager", "in", "Panama", ".", "of", "Unido", "Árabe"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "I-ORG", "B-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Central", ")", "CDP", "(", "Tennessee", ","], "ner_tags": ["B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["*", "Road", "20", "State", "Indiana", "px", "18"], "ner_tags": ["O", "I-ORG", "O", "I-ORG", "B-ORG", "O", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["It", "is", "known", "from", "Iran", "(", "Dag", "Kopet", ")", "and", "Turkmenistan", "."], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "I-LOC", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["(", "28", ")", "1–0", "Ewerthon"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER"]}
{"tokens": ["2014", "Women", "'s", "Futsal", "World", "Tournament"], "ner_tags": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["Guatemalan", "owl", "pygmy"], "ner_tags": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["LAC", "USC", "+"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Marion", "County", "Hardin", "Township", ",", ",", "Ohio"], "ner_tags": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["'", "'", "Maurie", "'", "Keane", "'", "''"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "I-PER", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["winged", "rough", "-", "swallow", "Northern"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "I-LOC", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["''", "Hypnotize", "opened", "with", "320,000", "copies", "the", "week", "first", "at", "1", "'", "on", "the", "Billboard", "200", "'", "''", ".", "''"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Caroline", "Hedwall", ")", "T12", "("], "ner_tags": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Winnie", "the", "Pooh", "(", "franchise", ")"], "ner_tags": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["O'", "J.", "Aubrey", "Brien"], "ner_tags": ["O", "I-PER", "B-PER", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Weverton", ",", "Maryland"], "ner_tags": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["Cleinias", "of", "Tarentum"], "ner_tags": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER"]}
{"tokens": ["Trained", "at", "Air", "Army", "Long", "Beach", "Field", ",", "California", ".", "inactivating", "then"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "eastward", "pressure", "to", "expand", "was", "created", "also", "by", "the", "inability", "to", "westward", "move", "inhibited", "by", "the", "presence", "formidable", "of", "the", "Flushing", "enormous", "Chinatown", ")", "法拉盛華埠", "(", "centered", "on", "Street", "Main", ",", "."], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "I-ORG", "B-ORG", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Arnold", "Schwarzenegger", "Robert", ",", "Patrick", "Edward", "Furlong", ",", ",", "Linda", "Hamilton"], "ner_tags": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "B-PER", "O", "I-PER", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER"]}
{"tokens": ["List", "of", "national", "libraries"], "ner_tags": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Banbury", "Banbury", "of", "Southam", "1st", "Baron", "Frederick", ","], "ner_tags": ["I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "B-PER", "I-PER"]}
{"tokens": ["'", "'", "?", "You", "Who", "Loves", "``"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Maryland", "Southern", "Blue", "Crabs", "**"], "ner_tags": ["I-ORG", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["(", "6", ")", "Casey", "Janssen"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER"]}
{"tokens": ["List", "of", "Ricans", "Puerto", "famous"], "ner_tags": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Simply", "''", "to", "Be", "``", "Meant", "with", "Jennifer", "(", "Warnes", ")"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "I-PER", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["''", "Rhodophthitus", "tricoloraria", "'", "'", "(", ",", "1890", "Mabille", ")"], "ner_tags": ["O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["II", "Leo", "of", "Galicia"], "ner_tags": ["I-PER", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER"]}
{"tokens": ["William", "Morrow", "and", "Company"], "ner_tags": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["is", "located", "The", "site", "between", "the", "Building", "War", "Memorial", "Baltimore", "City", "Hall", "and", "."], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "I-ORG", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Wusi", "Road", "(", "Subdistrict", ")"], "ner_tags": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "I-LOC", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Jane", "Levy", "Stephen", "Lang", ",", "Dylan", "Minnette", ","], "ner_tags": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["It", "is", "found", "in", "Costa", "Rica", "."], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["In", "1841", "the", "population", "of", "Norbury", "and", "Roston", "was", "510", ",", "414", "inhabitants", "were", "there", "in", "1895", "."], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["'", "Written", "by", "William", "Barton", "'", "''"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Lantenay", "(", "01206", ")"], "ner_tags": ["B-LOC", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["John", "Reeves", "(", "judge", ")"], "ner_tags": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER"]}
{"tokens": ["La", "(", "17113", ")", "Clotte"], "ner_tags": ["B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["Edwin", "(", "D", ")", "S.", "Johnson"], "ner_tags": ["B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "I-PER", "I-PER"]}
{"tokens": ["Funahashi", "(", "December", "25", ",", "1904", "–", "January", "13", ",", "1976", ")", "Seiichi"], "ner_tags": ["B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "I-PER"]}
{"tokens": ["It", "is", "known", "from", "Chile", "."], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["]", "AFL", "]", "(", "rules", "Australian", ")"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "I-ORG", "B-ORG", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Jolson", "Al", "were", "Among", "artists", "many", "who", "recorded", "this", "song", ".", "and", "Murray", "Billy"], "ner_tags": ["I-PER", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "I-PER", "B-PER"]}
{"tokens": ["'", "Duchy", "''", "William", "–", "V", "(", "995–1030", ")", "''", "of", "Aquitaine", "**"], "ner_tags": ["O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-PER", "O", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["''", "The", "Room", "Chris", ")", ",", "Tom", "Shapiro", "(", "Waters", "–", "3:40", "''"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Bahawalpur", "Zoo", "Punjab", ",", ",", "Bahawalpur"], "ner_tags": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "B-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Friedrich", "(", "1772–1800", ")", "Gilly"], "ner_tags": ["B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "I-PER"]}
{"tokens": ["****", "Longtail", "stingray", "(", "''D", "."], "ner_tags": ["O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "Woman", "Comes", "3:49", "``", ")", "Hall", "Daryl", "(", "''", "Goes", "and"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "I-PER", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["List", "of", "Orchidaceae", "genera"], "ner_tags": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Clarkston", "railway", "station"], "ner_tags": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Rimyongsu", "Sports", "Club", ")", "Sariwon", "("], "ner_tags": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-LOC", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["(", "1901–1907", ")", "Len", "Braund"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER"]}
{"tokens": ["Luther", ",", "King", "Martin", "Jr", "."], "ner_tags": ["I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER"]}
{"tokens": ["Verner", "Thomé", "(", "1878–1953", ")"], "ner_tags": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["College", "Brothers", "Presentation", "1944"], "ner_tags": ["I-ORG", "I-ORG", "B-ORG", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Jörgen", ",", "Sweden", "Olsson"], "ner_tags": ["B-PER", "O", "B-LOC", "I-PER"]}
{"tokens": ["He", "died", "in", "Oakland", ",", "California", "on", "March", "19", ",", "1979", "."], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["''", "Hands", "Too", "Many", "''", "(", "Meisner", "Randy", "–", "4:43", ",", "Don", "Felder", ")"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "I-PER", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Building", "Temple", "Masonic", ")", "Maywood", "(", "Illinois", ","], "ner_tags": ["I-ORG", "I-ORG", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Shake", "(", "company", ")"], "ner_tags": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "numerator", "and", "denominator", "consist", "normally", "of", "a", "number", "Fibonacci", "and", "its", "successor", "second", "."], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "I-ORG", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["In", "1976", "where", "he", "spent", "two", "seasons", "at", "Lions", "Leicester", "he", "joined", "his", "brother", "."], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "I-ORG", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["''", "Psolos", "fuligo", "fuligo", "'", "'", "'", "''", "Coon", "''", "—", "'"], "ner_tags": ["O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["(", "0", ")", "Sid", "Wilson"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER"]}
{"tokens": ["Jan", "Désirée", "Nosbusch", "Niklas", ","], "ner_tags": ["B-PER", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["**", "Trail", "1830–1838", ",", "of", "Tears"], "ner_tags": ["O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["Anders", "Nilsen", "Wiborg"], "ner_tags": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER"]}
{"tokens": ["States", "United", "Department", "of", "Labor"], "ner_tags": ["I-ORG", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["(", "9", ")", "Jared", "Dudley", "Jason", ",", "Richardson", "Emeka", "Okafor", ","], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "B-PER", "O", "I-PER", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Tomáš", "''", ")", "Round", "Third", "(", "Šmíd"], "ner_tags": ["B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "I-PER"]}
{"tokens": ["Chip", "(", "1986", ")", "Robinson"], "ner_tags": ["B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "I-PER"]}
{"tokens": ["St.", "Paisius", ".", "Orthodox", "Monastery", "Serbian", "Safford", ",", "Arizona", ","], "ner_tags": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "B-LOC", "O", "I-LOC", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Siege", "(", "542–43", ")", "of", "Naples"], "ner_tags": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Clarence", "Tommerson", ",", "NFL", "player"], "ner_tags": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Site", "Kill", "Naco-Mammoth"], "ner_tags": ["I-LOC", "I-LOC", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["'", "'", "Angiosperms", "'", "''", "'"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Communes", "of", "the", "Somme", "department"], "ner_tags": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["Magnificent", "eel", "snake"], "ner_tags": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["Menéndez", "Francisco", "Márquez"], "ner_tags": ["I-PER", "B-PER", "I-PER"]}
{"tokens": ["Beecher", ",", "Michigan", "–", "$", "13,484"], "ner_tags": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["in", "Lawn", "Green", "Cemetery", "he", "was", "interred", "After", "a", "large", "attended", "and", "well", "funeral", ",", "."], "ner_tags": ["O", "I-LOC", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["List", "of", "birds", "Indonesian", ":", "non-passerines"], "ner_tags": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Stade", "28", "Septembre", ",", "Conakry", "du"], "ner_tags": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["''", "'", "Gujranwala", "''", "'"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Ismail", "Musa", "Galal", "Haji"], "ner_tags": ["I-PER", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER"]}
{"tokens": ["in", "the", "Yanni", "album", "Voces", "''", "is", "included", "The", "song", "."], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Seethi", "K.", "M."], "ner_tags": ["I-PER", "B-PER", "I-PER"]}
{"tokens": ["East", "Chicago", ",", "Indiana"], "ner_tags": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["(", "town", ")", "Somerset", "Wisconsin", ","], "ner_tags": ["I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["Carter", ",", "Bonham", "Mark", "Carter", "-", "Baron", "Bonham"], "ner_tags": ["I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "I-PER", "I-PER"]}
{"tokens": ["'", "''", "Häkkinen", "Mika", "''", "'"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "I-PER", "B-PER", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Carolina", "South", "St.", "WTUA", "Stephen", ","], "ner_tags": ["I-LOC", "I-LOC", "B-LOC", "B-ORG", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["'", "'", "Kolkata", "''", "''"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["been", "has", "overthrown", "Taebong", "Goryeo", ",", "and", "established", "in", "the", "Korean", "peninsula", ".", "at", "Cheorwon", "Wang", "Kon", "ascends", "when", "the", "throne", ","], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["(", "2012", ")", "Sergey", "Shoygu"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER"]}
{"tokens": ["Tatem", "Elementary", "School", ",", "Collingswood", ",", "NJ"], "ner_tags": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["'", "Flick", "of", "the", "Switch", "'"], "ner_tags": ["O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["O.", "Owen", "L.", "(", "1898", ")"], "ner_tags": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["1911", "Building", "Portland", ",", "Oregon", "Yeon", ","], "ner_tags": ["O", "I-ORG", "B-LOC", "O", "I-LOC", "B-ORG", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["``", "'", "O", "Come", "All", "Faithful", "Ye", "'"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["District", "School", "Unified", "Valley", "Conejo"], "ner_tags": ["I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["Dick", "'s", "Sporting", "Goods", "ft²", ")", "80,000", "("], "ner_tags": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": [".", "Acianthera", "(", "Barb", "''", "rostellata", "''"], "ner_tags": ["O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "I-LOC", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Calhoun", "City", "Mississippi", ","], "ner_tags": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["Rockhead", "(", "fish", ")"], "ner_tags": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["Lawn", "Cedar", "Jersey", "New", "Cemetery", ",", "Paterson", ","], "ner_tags": ["I-LOC", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["''", "CONCACAF", "Champions", "'", ":", "Cup", "'", "'", "'"], "ner_tags": ["O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["It", "in", "1939", "was", "described", "by", "Breuning", "."], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Pontianak", ")", "folklore", "("], "ner_tags": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER"]}
{"tokens": ["Myrtle", "Beach", "States", "United", ","], "ner_tags": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-LOC", "B-LOC", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Tremoschna", ":", "Třemošná", "B,60"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "B-LOC", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["'", "to", "Save", "How", "a", "Life", "'"], "ner_tags": ["O", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Parken", "(", "H", ")", ",", "Copenhagen"], "ner_tags": ["B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["Tenerife", "Canary", "Islands", ",", "Spain", ","], "ner_tags": ["B-LOC", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Sui", "Wenjing", "/", "Han", "Cong"], "ner_tags": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER"]}
{"tokens": ["under", "Now", "control", "of", "482nd", "Wing", "Fighter", "Fighter", "125th", "Wing", ",", "Air", "National", "Florida", "Guard", "(", ")", "Detachment", "1", "and", "Force", "Air", "Reserve", "Command", "(", ")"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "I-ORG", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["אֶת", "חֶבְרוֹן", "וְאֶת", "מִגְרָשֶׁה", "ָ"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["(", "район", "Вознесенський", ")", "Voznesensk"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["Chimneys", "of", "Generating", "Poolbeg", "Station"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "I-ORG", "B-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["This", "Hour", "Has", "cast", "22", "Minutes", "''"], "ner_tags": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Warkentin", "Bernhard", "Homestead"], "ner_tags": ["I-ORG", "B-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["She", "lives", "currently", "in", "Los", "Angeles", "California", ",", "."], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "B-LOC", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Same", "applied", "to", "Americans", "Polish", "."], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "I-ORG", "B-ORG", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["It", "was", "discovered", "in", "Oxyrhynchus", "."], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Princess", "Clémentine", "of", "Belgium"], "ner_tags": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER"]}
{"tokens": ["Andrex", ")", "actor", "("], "ner_tags": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER"]}
{"tokens": ["''", "Sheen", "Martin", "The", "Wing", "West", "-"], "ner_tags": ["O", "I-PER", "B-PER", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["''", "U", "Got", "It", "Bad", "``"], "ner_tags": ["O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["completed", "Reservoir", "Hanningfield", "in", "1957"], "ner_tags": ["O", "I-LOC", "B-LOC", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Bright", "Size", "Life", "–", "Pat", "Metheny", "''"], "ner_tags": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Vulcana", "(", "1875–1946", ")"], "ner_tags": ["B-PER", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Society", "of", "the", "Friends", "of", "Truth"], "ner_tags": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER"]}
{"tokens": ["frog", "Indian", "flying"], "ner_tags": ["I-LOC", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["Dam", "Knightville", "Westfield", "River", "–"], "ner_tags": ["I-LOC", "B-LOC", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Aborigines", "'", "Protection", "Society"], "ner_tags": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Municipality", "Regional", "County", "Memphrémagog"], "ner_tags": ["I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["were", "All", "three", "goals", "of", "the", "match", "scored", "by", "Xherdan", "Shaqiri", "."], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["''", "'", "CBS", "''", "'"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["*", "1951", "-", "1980", "Sir", "Hawthorne", "Rede", "William"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER"]}
{"tokens": ["Jr", ".", "Brownell", "Herbert", ","], "ner_tags": ["I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "B-PER", "I-PER"]}
{"tokens": ["(", "1863–1900", ")", "George", "Caspar", "Adams"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER"]}
{"tokens": ["Franz", "Papen", "von"], "ner_tags": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER"]}
{"tokens": ["Lee", "Trevino", "won", "the", "tournaments", "most", ",", "six", "."], "ner_tags": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["East", "Brunswick", ".", "New", ",", "Jersey"], "ner_tags": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["(", "1", ")", "Dave", "Righetti"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER"]}
{"tokens": ["Head", "of", "government", ":"], "ner_tags": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["by", "Fats", "Recorded", "Waller", "."], "ner_tags": ["O", "B-PER", "O", "I-PER", "O"]}
{"tokens": [":", "Kaho", "Onodera", "''", "'", "Second", "''", "'"], "ner_tags": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Leopold", "Grand", "Duke", "of", "Baden", ","], "ner_tags": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER"]}
{"tokens": ["Oriole", "Park", ",", "States", "United", "in", "Baltimore", ",", "Maryland", "at", "Camden", "Yards"], "ner_tags": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-LOC", "B-LOC", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Route", "Massachusetts", "3A"], "ner_tags": ["I-ORG", "B-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Fulvio", "(", "1988", ")", "Ballabio"], "ner_tags": ["B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "I-PER"]}
{"tokens": ["elements", "of", "signs", "(", "Peirce", ")", "Semiotic", "and", "classes"], "ner_tags": ["I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Meigs", "Township", ",", "Muskingum", "County", ",", "Ohio"], "ner_tags": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["was", "He", "born", "in", "Glasgow", "Scotland", ",", "."], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "B-LOC", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Tarnów", "Opolski", "Gmina"], "ner_tags": ["I-LOC", "I-LOC", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["his", "Cortés", "Hernán", "was", "relative", ",", "he", "accompanied", "to", "Mexico", "(", "Spain", "New", ")", "whom", "in", "1526", "."], "ner_tags": ["O", "I-PER", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "I-LOC", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["File", "Tiananmen", ":", "(", "天安门", ")"], "ner_tags": ["O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": [":", "Episode", "My", "It", "'s", "and", "I", "'ll", "Lie", "if", "I", "Want", "Party", "``"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "I-ORG", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["He", "died", "in", "Boca", "Raton", ",", "Florida", "on", "August", "25", ",", "1992", "."], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["''", "(", "1988", ")", "Nothin", "'", "But", "Trouble", "''"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "O"]}
{"tokens": [",", "County", "McLeod", "Township", "Lynn", ",", "Minnesota"], "ner_tags": ["I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["Communes", "of", "the", "Côte", "-d", "'", "Or", "department"], "ner_tags": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["He", "resides", "in", "Monmouth", "Junction", "New", ",", "Jersey", "."], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Gods", "Radio", "FM"], "ner_tags": ["I-ORG", "I-ORG", "B-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Tolkien", "R.", "R.", "J."], "ner_tags": ["I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "B-PER"]}
{"tokens": ["Up", "'", "''", "Speed", "''", "'"], "ner_tags": ["I-ORG", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["*36th", "on", "November", "10", "2005", ",", "Calgary", "CAN"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["Paul", "(", "2007", ")", "Tang"], "ner_tags": ["B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "I-PER"]}
{"tokens": ["Melissa", "(", "1945", "–1947", ")", "Hayden"], "ner_tags": ["B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "I-PER"]}
{"tokens": ["He", "is", "a", "brother", "of", "the", "pianist", "noted", "Chilly", "Gonzales", "."], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Peru", ":", "Party", "Communist", "Peruvian"], "ner_tags": ["B-LOC", "O", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "B-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Morris", "Pat", "(", "musician", ")"], "ner_tags": ["I-PER", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER"]}
{"tokens": ["It", "is", "found", "in", "Australia", ",", "where", "been", "has", "it", "recorded", "from", "Australia", "Western", "."], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "B-LOC", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Waveguide", ")", "optics", "("], "ner_tags": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["Las", "Cruces", ",", "Mexico", "New"], "ner_tags": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["6–4", ",", "7", "–6", "(", "7–3", ")", ",", "/", "Sitak", "Artem", "Radu", "Albot"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "I-PER", "B-PER", "B-PER", "I-PER"]}
{"tokens": ["by", "Arthur", "Byron", "Cover", "``"], "ner_tags": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["''", "Aletia", "infrargyrea", "'", "'"], "ner_tags": ["O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["All", "songs", ".", "composed", "by", "Leonard", "Bernstein", "Sondheim", "and", "Stephen"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-PER"]}
{"tokens": ["H.", ")", "D", "(", "Morrison", "James"], "ner_tags": ["I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "I-PER", "B-PER"]}
{"tokens": ["*", "10,000", "m", ":", "'", "27:28.12", "''", "min", "''", "'", "Neerpelt", ",", "June", "2007", "–", "2"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["His", "victory", "official", "second", "came", "at", "9:45", "am", "on", "May", "6", "he", "which", "shared", "with", "Ernst", "Leman", "Alexander", "and", "Kazakov", ",", "followed", ",", "by", "his", "third", "on", "April", "21", "."], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "B-PER", "O", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "Dozen", "Dirty", "Brass", "Band"], "ner_tags": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["de", "Márcio", "Rogério", "Andrade"], "ner_tags": ["I-PER", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER"]}
{"tokens": ["(", "Japan", ")", "Marshal"], "ner_tags": ["I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "B-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Cephissus", "(", "Athenian", "plain", ")"], "ner_tags": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["Francis", "Wayland", "Parker"], "ner_tags": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER"]}
{"tokens": ["'", "ceratosperma", "''", "Valsa", "'"], "ner_tags": ["O", "I-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["St", "'s", "Ann", "College"], "ner_tags": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["``", "I", "Promise", "to", "Wait", "Love", "My", "'", "'"], "ner_tags": ["O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Nursing", "National", "Week", ")", "States", "United", "("], "ner_tags": ["I-ORG", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "I-LOC", "B-LOC", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["1897", ":", "Chicago", "v.", "Chicago", "'", "'", "&", "Quincy", "Burlington", ",", "Railroad"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["he", "had", "an", "interview", "with", "Will", "''", "of", "Life", ".", "Lang", "Jr", "In", "1947", ",", "to", "discuss", "his", "life", "and", "his", "role", "as", "a", "receptionist", "."], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "Room", "Outdoor"], "ner_tags": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": [":", "Hell", "The", "Sequel", "''"], "ner_tags": ["I-ORG", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["He", "was", "educated", "at", "the", "School", "Community", "High", "then", "College", "Technical", "Carlisle", "and", "Tehran", ",", "."], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "I-ORG", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "B-ORG", "O", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["he", "joined", "In", "1960", ",", "the", "Army", "U.S.", ".", "for", "three", "years", "being", "stationed", "in", "Germany", ","], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "I-ORG", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["High", "School", "No.8", "Beijing"], "ner_tags": ["I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "B-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Ashdot", "from", "Ashdot", "Ya'akov", ",", "(", "1924", ",", "1933", ")", "Meuhad", "(", "1953", ")", "Ya'akov"], "ner_tags": ["B-ORG", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Lacs", "Conzieu", "de"], "ner_tags": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["Monmouth", ",", "–", "$", "15,839", "Illinois"], "ner_tags": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["Region", "Anatolia", "Eastern"], "ner_tags": ["I-LOC", "I-LOC", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["He", "died", "in", "Williamsport", "Pennsylvania", ",", "in", "July", "of", "1969", "."], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Returning", "to", "Norfolk", "Virginia", ",", ",", "1", "April", "1946", ",", "at", "Baltimore", ",", "25", "April", "1946", "Maryland", ",", "was", "decommissioned", "''", "Calamares", "''", ".", "and", "returned", "to", "the", "War", "Shipping", "Administration", ","], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "I-LOC", "O", "B-ORG", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "I-ORG", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["Platon", ")", "Kulbusch", "("], "ner_tags": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER"]}
{"tokens": ["F.C", ".", "Southampton"], "ner_tags": ["I-ORG", "I-ORG", "B-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Chuuk", "flying", "fox"], "ner_tags": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["Holles", "John", "Earl", "2nd", "of", "Clare", ","], "ner_tags": ["I-PER", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "Conservation", "Churches", "Trust", "now", "cares", "for", "the", "building", "."], "ner_tags": ["O", "I-ORG", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["They", "originate", "from", "Asia", "South", "East", "and", "Africa", ",", "Middle", "East", ",", "Europe", ",", "."], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "I-LOC", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "I-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Up", "Growing", ")", "The", "Primetime", "T.G.I.S.", "("], "ner_tags": ["I-ORG", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["the", "building", "was", "turned", "Following", "its", "sale", "by", "the", "Railways", "New", "Zealand", "Corporation", "in", "the", "1990s", ",", "into", "student", "accommodation", "by", "Auckland", "University", ".", "been", "has", "occupied", "by", "private", "apartments", "and", "since", "2008"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "I-ORG", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Çıraqlı", ",", "Lachin"], "ner_tags": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["Sağkaya", ",", "Ceyhan"], "ner_tags": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["He", "is", "from", "Andhra", "Pradesh", "in", "South", "India", "."], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Wing", "53d", ")", "WG", "53", "("], "ner_tags": ["I-ORG", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Oda", "Station", "(", "小田駅", ")", ")", "Shimane", "("], "ner_tags": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Tales", "from", "Turnpike", "House", "'", "'"], "ner_tags": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Aboudeïa", "–", "Region", "Salamat"], "ner_tags": ["B-ORG", "O", "I-LOC", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": [")", "Gyeongsang", "South", "(", "Gibaeksan"], "ner_tags": ["I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["Rufus", "Choate", "(", "W-MA", ")"], "ner_tags": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["'", "Albright", "'", "Tony", "'", "'", "''"], "ner_tags": ["O", "I-PER", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Live", "''", "Run", "to", "the", "Water", "``", "-"], "ner_tags": ["B-ORG", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Kunio", "Maekawa", ",", "architect"], "ner_tags": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["'", "Kingdom", "–", "William", "the", "Lion", "(", "1165–1214", ")", "''", "of", "Scotland", "''"], "ner_tags": ["O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["2008", "Morgenstern", "Janusz", ":"], "ner_tags": ["O", "I-PER", "B-PER", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["''", "Platanthera", "bifolia", "'", "'"], "ner_tags": ["O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["with", "Swindon", "Town", "he", "played", "in", "the", "Premier", "League", "for", "whom", ",", "spent", "He", "much", "of", "his", "career", "."], "ner_tags": ["O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["UEFA", "Women", "'s", "Euro", "2013"], "ner_tags": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["It", "followed", "then", "the", "Williamson", "Sprague", "Rivers", "and", "claiming", "parts", "large", "of", "the", "Klamath", "Indian", "Reservation", ",", "."], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Mumbai–"], "ner_tags": ["O"]}
{"tokens": ["'", "''", "Toulouse", "''"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "B-LOC", "O"]}
{"tokens": [",", "Hamer", "LL.M.", "Rupert", "MLC", ","], "ner_tags": ["O", "I-PER", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": [".", "Zar", "Ka", "-", "vol", "''"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["(", "1", ")", "Masters", "of", "Darts"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER"]}
{"tokens": ["We", "Go", ",", "Stays", "Time", "''"], "ner_tags": ["I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "B-ORG", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Listed", "buildings", "in", "Crawley"], "ner_tags": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Michel", "(", "1752–1755", ")", "Ange", "Duquesne", "Menneville", "de", "-"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Poříčí", "Sázavou", "nad"], "ner_tags": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["J.", "J.", "and", "Kai", "Winding", "Johnson"], "ner_tags": ["B-PER", "B-PER", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER"]}
{"tokens": ["Rosario", "Francisco", "Sánchez", "and", "Ramón", "Matías", "Mella", "del", "Juan", ",", "Pablo", "Duarte"], "ner_tags": ["I-PER", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "I-PER", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "B-PER", "O", "I-PER", "I-PER"]}
{"tokens": ["Rupert", "as", "Sir", ",", "Lord", "Pembroke", "Herbert", "William", "Young"], "ner_tags": ["B-PER", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER"]}
{"tokens": ["plover", "-bellied", "Black", ",", "''", "Pluvialis", "squatarola", "'", "'"], "ner_tags": ["I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["He", "is", "a", "goalkeeper", "for", "Lech", "Poznań", "."], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Hardeman", ")", "D", "(", "Thomas", ".", "Jr", ","], "ner_tags": ["I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER"]}
{"tokens": ["V.", "Johannes", "Jensen"], "ner_tags": ["I-PER", "B-PER", "I-PER"]}
{"tokens": ["Sean", "Lockhart", "Paul"], "ner_tags": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER"]}
{"tokens": ["District", "Văn", "Lãng"], "ner_tags": ["I-LOC", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["were", "selected", "67", "competitors", "by", "the", "DLV", "."], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Kalbar", ",", "Queensland"], "ner_tags": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["Bobby", "'s", "Burger", "Palace"], "ner_tags": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Beulah", "(", "1888–1981", ")", "Bondi"], "ner_tags": ["B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "I-PER"]}
{"tokens": ["Pelican", "Rapids", ",", "–", "$", "13,699", "Minnesota"], "ner_tags": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["This", "as", "ISSN", "0038-5573", "was", "published", "by", "the", "Mathematical", "American", "Society", "."], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "I-ORG", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Trilofo", ",", "Arcadia"], "ner_tags": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["Melissa", ",", "Texas"], "ner_tags": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "Times", "''", "(", "Chicago", ")", "''", "went", "in", "2005", "defunct", ","], "ner_tags": ["O", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Helsby", "Baron", "Laurence", "Helsby", ","], "ner_tags": ["I-PER", "I-PER", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER"]}
{"tokens": ["Ronaldinho", "'s", "Gaucho", "Team"], "ner_tags": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Rüppell", "'s", "robin-chat"], "ner_tags": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["Thomas", "'s", "pine", "vole"], "ner_tags": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["Tennessee", "in", "the", "Civil", "War"], "ner_tags": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Brass", "''", "Minarete", "(", "2010", ")"], "ner_tags": ["I-ORG", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["*2008", "–", "``", "All", "Summer", "Long", "''", "–", "Kid", "Rock"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER"]}
{"tokens": ["Al", "Nahyan", "Mubarak", "Hamdan", "bin"], "ner_tags": ["I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "B-PER", "I-PER"]}
{"tokens": ["It", "'s", "No", "Good"], "ner_tags": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Fork", "North", "Flathead", ",", "States", "United", "Canada", "-"], "ner_tags": ["I-LOC", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "I-LOC", "B-LOC", "B-LOC", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["''", "DCLXVI", "To", "Ride", "Shoot", "Speak", "and", "the", "Truth", "Straight", ":"], "ner_tags": ["O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["McCoy", "''", "(", "1975", "-", "1976", ")"], "ner_tags": ["B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "Price", "Is", "Right", ")", "show", "game", "Philippine", "(", "'", "'"], "ner_tags": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["''", "Northern", "March", "''", "Lothair", "–", "(", "983–1003", ")", "'", "***"], "ner_tags": ["O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["'", "'", "'", "Kentucky", "'", "''"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["He", "claimed", "to", "be", "son", "of", "Khalilullah", "II", "."], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["''", "(", "Zeller", ",", "1847", ")", "Dialectica", "imperialella", "''"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Royal", "Australian", "Corps", "of", "Transport", "-", "The", "Princess", "Royal"], "ner_tags": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "B-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["City", "Johor", "Bahru", "Square"], "ner_tags": ["I-ORG", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["is", "It", "known", "from", "Kenya", "and", "Uganda", "."], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["*9378", "-", "'", "burgessi", "Apamea", "'"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "I-LOC", "B-LOC", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Shooting", "forward", "guard", "/", "Small"], "ner_tags": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-PER"]}
{"tokens": ["Marty", "Mount", "College", "Yankton", "(", "South", "Dakota", ",", ")"], "ner_tags": ["I-ORG", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "B-LOC", "O", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Three", "'s", "a", "Crowd"], "ner_tags": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["'", "''", "APEC", "'", "Persiaran", "''"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "I-ORG", "O", "B-ORG", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["''", "Theretra", "jugurtha", "''", ",", "1875", "(", "Boisduval", ")"], "ner_tags": ["O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["School", "Business", "Harvard", "(", "2013", ")", "Press", "Up", "Managing", "Solutions", "Expert", "to", "Challenges", "Everyday", ":"], "ner_tags": ["I-ORG", "I-ORG", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Marysville", ",", "Pennsylvania"], "ner_tags": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["St.", "'s", "Mary", "Church", ",", "Stoneham", "South"], "ner_tags": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["He", "was", "a", "son", "of", "Wolfgang", "Amadeus", "Mozart", "."], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["It", "has", "also", "been", "introduced", "to", "Australia", "and", "the", "Philippines", "the", "Galápagos", "Islands", ",", "Madeira", ",", "."], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["from", "Søgne", "hailed", "He", "."], "ner_tags": ["O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["(", "1983–87", ")", "Njego", "Pesa"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER"]}
{"tokens": ["'", "Melandri", "''", "Marco", "'", "'", "'"], "ner_tags": ["O", "I-PER", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Quan", "Sun", "Hitomi", ":", "Nabatame"], "ner_tags": ["I-PER", "B-PER", "I-ORG", "O", "B-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Clarke", "David", "(", "Paralympic", "footballer", ")"], "ner_tags": ["I-PER", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER"]}
{"tokens": ["Comanche", ",", "Oklahoma"], "ner_tags": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["in", "1912", ".", "from", "the", "University", "of", "Wisconsin", "Law", "School", "He", "received", "his", "LL.B", "."], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Bova", ",", "Calabria"], "ner_tags": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["Lamb", "'s", "Conduit", "Field"], "ner_tags": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["Doug", ",", "Keith", "Barron", "McClure"], "ner_tags": ["B-PER", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER"]}
{"tokens": ["It", "south", "southeast", "of", "Willits", "-", "at", "an", "elevation", "of", "1916", "feet", ")", "584", "m", "(", ",", "is", "located", "on", "the", "Northwestern", "Pacific", "Railroad", "."], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["``", "I", "'ll", "Walk", "''"], "ner_tags": ["O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Silver", "Vegas", "Nevada", ",", "Slipper", "Las", ","], "ner_tags": ["B-ORG", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "I-ORG", "B-LOC", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Top", "Chef", "'", "Desserts", "'", "Just", ":"], "ner_tags": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "I-ORG", "O", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Up", "'", "Wake", "Brother", "'", "``"], "ner_tags": ["I-ORG", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["green", "pigeon", "Pemba"], "ner_tags": ["I-LOC", "I-LOC", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["''", "Mautz", "'", "B.", "Robert", "''", "'"], "ner_tags": ["O", "I-PER", "O", "I-PER", "B-PER", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Frankfurt", "Festhalle", "Hesse", ",", ",", "Frankfurt"], "ner_tags": ["I-ORG", "B-ORG", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["``", "Merchant", "Carnival", "''", "Natalie", "–"], "ner_tags": ["O", "I-PER", "B-ORG", "O", "B-PER", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Fati", "Ali", "Al", "Mishad", "Sharif"], "ner_tags": ["I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "B-PER"]}
{"tokens": ["Talal", "Muhammad", "bin", "Prince"], "ner_tags": ["I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "B-PER"]}
{"tokens": ["2000", "-", "Servants", "of", "Darkness", "'", "'"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["(", "1994-1997", ")", "McLellan", "Anne"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "I-PER", "B-PER"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "demand", "is", "$", "."], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["1565", "(", "died", "MP", ")", "Morgan", "Thomas"], "ner_tags": ["I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "B-PER"]}
{"tokens": ["'", "Fisichella", "''", "Giancarlo", "'", "'", "'"], "ner_tags": ["O", "I-PER", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "People", "'s", "Petition"], "ner_tags": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["He", "was", "Mayor", ".", "July", "1414", "of", "Exeter", "to", "October", "1415"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Brays", "Oaks", ",", "Houston"], "ner_tags": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["He", "is", "also", "a", "member", "of", "the", "Qatar", "basketball", "national", "team", "."], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["He", "became", "a", "journalist", "for", "The", "Nashville", "American", "''", "from", "1885", "to", "1892", "serving", "as", "a", "correspondent", ",", "."], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Bay", "Evans", "is", "nearby", "."], "ner_tags": ["I-LOC", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["**", "Basilica", "of", "San", "Isidoro", "León", ",", ",", "consecrated", "Spain", "."], "ner_tags": ["O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "I-LOC", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Sir", "Gilbert", ",", ")", "died", "1785", "(", "Heathcote", "Baronet", "3rd"], "ner_tags": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER"]}
{"tokens": ["Lee", ",", "LF", "(", "1965", "-1966", ")", "Maye"], "ner_tags": ["B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "I-PER"]}
{"tokens": ["''", ":", "Venue", "'", "Daegu", "Civic", "Stadium", ",", "Daegu", "''", "'"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Cacherano", "Osasco", "Policarpo", "d'"], "ner_tags": ["I-PER", "O", "B-PER", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["elections", "Parliamentary", "on", "22", "September", "2002", "44.1", "%", "of", "the", "vote", "primary", ":"], "ner_tags": ["I-ORG", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Elachista", "''", "quadripunctella", ")", "Hübner", ",", "1825", "(", "''"], "ner_tags": ["B-LOC", "O", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["is", "found", "It", "in", "Cameroon", "and", "Príncipe", "and", "São", "Tomé", "."], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "I-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Rupert", "Keegan", "took", "the", "B.A.R.C", "."], "ner_tags": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Miranda", "(", "1993", "-", ")", "Cosgrove"], "ner_tags": ["B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "I-PER"]}
{"tokens": ["Uluçınar", ",", "İmamoğlu"], "ner_tags": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["Arrese", "Luis", "de", "José"], "ner_tags": ["I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "B-PER"]}
{"tokens": ["''", "65", "Damien", "G", "Woody", "(", "IR", ")", "7", "px"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Joppatowne", ",", "Maryland"], "ner_tags": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["John", "Pratt", "Marquess", "1st", ",", "Camden"], "ner_tags": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER"]}
{"tokens": ["'", "Evancho", "Jackie", "''", ")", "2000", "born", "(", "''"], "ner_tags": ["O", "I-PER", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["NALSAR"], "ner_tags": ["B-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Toronto", ",", "CITY", "Ontario", "-"], "ner_tags": ["B-LOC", "O", "B-ORG", "B-LOC", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Mark", "Martin", "and", "Keselowski", "Brad", "followed", "with", "41", "points", "each", "in", "third", "and", "fourth", ".", ",", "and", "was", "one", "ahead", "of", "Ryan", "Newman", "in", "fifth"], "ner_tags": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "I-PER", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["'", "'", "Livin", "``", "on", "Time", "Borrowed", "'"], "ner_tags": ["I-ORG", "I-ORG", "B-ORG", "O", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Luis", "José", "Reséndez"], "ner_tags": ["I-PER", "B-PER", "I-PER"]}
{"tokens": ["internally", "the", "song", "and", "performer", "chose", "RAI", "Broadcaster", "."], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Theater", "''", "Science", "Mystery", "3000"], "ner_tags": ["I-ORG", "O", "I-ORG", "B-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["J.", "Kelso", "J."], "ner_tags": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "B-PER"]}
{"tokens": ["Events", "'", "'", "''", "1983", "in", "Sweden", "''", "from", "the", "year"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Islamic", "State", "2,300", ":", "and", "the", "Levant", "of", "Iraq"], "ner_tags": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["Byzantium", "under", "the", "Macedonians"], "ner_tags": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Johan", "Caspar", "Cicignon", "von"], "ner_tags": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER"]}
{"tokens": ["North", "Vacherie", ",", "Louisiana"], "ner_tags": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["Dick", "Hippodrome", "Birmingham", "(", "2010–2011", ")", "''", "Whittington", "-"], "ner_tags": ["B-PER", "I-LOC", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "I-PER", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["–", "Shakira", "''", "Ojos", "``", "Así"], "ner_tags": ["O", "B-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["North", "Woodbridge", ",", "California"], "ner_tags": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["''", ",", "1791", ")", "Giorna", "(", "puerpera", "Catocala", "''"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "I-LOC", "B-LOC", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["List", "of", "counties", "in", "Missouri"], "ner_tags": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "Threshold", "of", "a", "Persona"], "ner_tags": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["''", "funebrana", "''", "Grapholita", "Treitschke", ",", "1835"], "ner_tags": ["O", "I-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Rube", "Ellis", "(", "1911", ")"], "ner_tags": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["*", "1986", ":", "Franke", "'", "Endzeit", "''", "'", "W.", "Herbert", ","], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "I-PER", "B-PER", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Miranda", "Azán", "de"], "ner_tags": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["'", "'", "Kepong", "'", "'", "Bukit", "''"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["National", "Volcanoes", "Park", ",", "Rwanda"], "ner_tags": ["I-LOC", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["Terry", "George", "(", "entrepreneur", ")"], "ner_tags": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER"]}
{"tokens": ["Based", "in", "Lille", "Versailles", "and", "."], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "B-LOC", "B-LOC", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "Battle", "Bennington", "Monument", ".", "in", "Bennington", ",", "1889", "Vermont", ",", "*"], "ner_tags": ["O", "I-ORG", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-LOC", "O", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["College", "–", "Westwood", "Dallas", "Texas", ","], "ner_tags": ["I-ORG", "O", "B-ORG", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Anabelle", "Langlois", "Patrice", "Archetto", "/"], "ner_tags": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Nino", "Mario", "Vaccarella", "Ignazio", "Andretti", "Giunti"], "ner_tags": ["B-PER", "B-PER", "I-PER", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER"]}
{"tokens": ["Part", "of", "the", "Main", "Line", "state-owned", "of", "Works", "Public"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["(", "4", "–12", "yrs", ")", "Tannat", "Madiran"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "B-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Wasikowska", "Mia", "as", "Alice", "Kingsleigh", "."], "ner_tags": ["I-PER", "B-PER", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["he", "In", "1969", "was", "posthumously", "inducted", "into", "the", "Swimming", "International", "Hall", "of", "Fame", "."], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "I-ORG", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["It", "consists", "of", "the", "3", "Bundesautobahn", "the", "Bundesautobahn", "4", ",", "the", "Bundesautobahn", "1", "and", "."], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "I-ORG", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["five", "winners", "to", "date", "Leanne", ":", "and", "Kevin", "Simm", "McCrorie", "Stevie", ",", "Mitchell", "Andrea", ",", "Begley", "Jermain", ",", "Jackman", "have", "There", "been", "."], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-ORG", "B-ORG", "O", "I-PER", "B-PER", "O", "I-PER", "B-PER", "O", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["(", "1534–1619", ")", "Francesco", "Soto", "Langa", "de"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER"]}
{"tokens": ["Township", ",", "County", "Jefferson", "Pennsylvania", ",", "Porter"], "ner_tags": ["I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["Washington", "County", "Butler", "Township", ",", "Iowa", ","], "ner_tags": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["2013", "Africa", "Cup", "of", "Nations", "qualification"], "ner_tags": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["two", "main", "branches", "of", "the", "family", ",", "one", "in", "Dutton", "and", "the", "other", "in", "Sutton", "Weaver", "were", "There", "."], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Decius", "(", "249-251", ")"], "ner_tags": ["B-PER", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": [":", "3", "(", "2003", ",", "2004", ",", "2005", ")", "Seán", "hAilpín", "Óg", "Ó"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER"]}
{"tokens": ["several", "trips", "Has", "made", "to", "the", "Middle", "East", ".", "troops", "visiting", "in", "Iraq", "and", "Afghanistan", ",", "visiting", "as", "well", "as", "Kyrgyzstan", "Kuwait", ",", "and", "Qatar", ",", "Afghanistan", "Bahrain", ",", "Arabia", "Saudi", ",", "the", "Emirates", "Arab", "United", ",", ",", "*"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "B-LOC", "O", "I-LOC", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["''", "–", "2:16", "Last", "Date", "''", "Floyd", "Cramer", "(", ")"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Giovanni", "Buonamente", "Battista"], "ner_tags": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER"]}
{"tokens": ["Tazmania", "''", "(", "2006", ")"], "ner_tags": ["B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["'", "''", "Marcello", "'", "Trotta", "'", "'"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "I-PER", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["2369", "Shickshinny", ",", "$", "14,880", "Pennsylvania"], "ner_tags": ["O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["yellow", "finch", "Patagonian"], "ner_tags": ["I-LOC", "I-LOC", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["''", "President", "'s", "'", "Cup", "'", "''"], "ner_tags": ["O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "I-ORG", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Grimby", "-", "Dumont", "Richard", "Mr.", "*"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "I-PER", "B-PER", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["''", "Forever", "Memorial", "Tokimeki", "With", ":"], "ner_tags": ["O", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["''", "Arnaud", "Boetsch", "'", ")", "round", "Second", "(", "'"], "ner_tags": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["'", "Soto", "''", "Lornna", "'", "''"], "ner_tags": ["O", "I-PER", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["It", "premiered", "on", "27", ".", "on", "YouTube", "June", "2010"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Damon", "(", "3,018", ")", "Stoudamire"], "ner_tags": ["B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "I-PER"]}
{"tokens": ["Bill", ",", "Peter", ",", "Buck", "Stipe", "Michael", "Berry", ",", "Mike", "Mills"], "ner_tags": ["B-PER", "O", "B-PER", "O", "I-PER", "I-PER", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER"]}
{"tokens": ["River", "Călineasa", "Cald", ")", "Someșul", "("], "ner_tags": ["I-LOC", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["Camille", "Paglia", "compares", "the", "image", "to", "William", "Blake", "'s", "''", "engravings", "of", "contorted", "solipsistically", "figures", "``", "resulting", "."], "ner_tags": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Assemblyman", "Peter", "Barnes", "J.", "III", ")", "D", "("], "ner_tags": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["In", "1854", "was", "he", "appointed", "to", "a", "seat", "on", "the", "Council", "of", "Nova", "Scotia", "Legislative", "upon", "the", "recommendation", "of", "William", "Young", ",", "."], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "I-ORG", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Mark", "(", "2010–2011", ")", "McGrath"], "ner_tags": ["B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "I-PER"]}
{"tokens": ["File", ".", "Southern", "Italy", "on", "the", "1849", "map", ":", "and", "Sicily"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["Petersburg", ",", "Virginia"], "ner_tags": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["His", "descendants", "include", "Vincenzo", "Viviani", "a", "disciple", ",", "and", "biographer", "of", "Galileo", "Galilei", "."], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["This", "was", "continued", "by", "his", "sons", "Alexander", ",", "I", "Edgar", "David", "in", "particular", "and", "I", "."], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "I-PER", "B-PER", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "I-PER", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["He", "in", "was", "Sworn", "on", "January", "4", "2011", "as", "a", "Member", "of", "the", "Queen", "'s", "Privy", "Council", "for", "Canada", "."], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["John", ",", "Crichton", "Viscount", "Henry", "Crichton"], "ner_tags": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "song", "at", "Lodge", "Grouse", "was", "recorded", "under", "the", "supervision", "of", "producer", "Lee", "Jacknife", ",", "."], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "I-ORG", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "I-PER", "B-PER", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Krapanj", "170", ",", "population"], "ner_tags": ["B-LOC", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Garan", "Jr", "E.", "Fossum", "Michael", ",", "J.", "Ronald", "."], "ner_tags": ["I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "B-PER", "I-PER"]}
{"tokens": ["San", "Pablo", "y", "Pedro", "Asistencia", "San"], "ner_tags": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "B-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["''", "hemistacta", "Telamoptilia", ")", ",", "1918", "Meyrick", "(", "''"], "ner_tags": ["O", "I-LOC", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["(", "A", ")", ",", "knot", "Calidris", "canutus", "''", "''", "Red"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["Mer", "–", "57,553", "Seyne-sur", "La", "-"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["border", "Harnedy", "''", "Séamus", "'"], "ner_tags": ["O", "I-PER", "O", "B-PER", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["**", "Western", "gorilla", ".", "(", "''G"], "ner_tags": ["O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Volume", "Lyraka", "(", "2010", ")", "'", "'", "1"], "ner_tags": ["I-ORG", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["''", "'", "Brunei", "'", "'", "'"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Inscription", "Hälsingland", "Rune", "21"], "ner_tags": ["I-LOC", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": [",", "Joe", "Abercrombie", ";", "author"], "ner_tags": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Reinhold", "Fred", "Savage", "Judge", ","], "ner_tags": ["I-PER", "B-PER", "I-PER", "B-PER", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Craven", "delta", "''", "Melaleuca"], "ner_tags": ["B-PER", "I-LOC", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "Beatles", "'", "influence", "on", "culture", "popular"], "ner_tags": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER"]}
{"tokens": ["in", "an", "episode", "of", "Unsolved", "Mysteries", "''", "was", "profiled", "His", "death", "."], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["''", ")", ",", "1759", "Clerck", "(", "Agrochola", "lota", "''"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Highest", "total", "against", ":", "224", "/", "7", "by", "Somerset", "at", "Taunton", ",", "2015"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["pseudoparvula", "Mordellistena", "''", "Ermisch", ",", "1956", "''"], "ner_tags": ["I-LOC", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["All", "Saints", "Cathedral", ",", "Halifax"], "ner_tags": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Beginning", "of", "Karoo", "Ice", "Age", "."], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["is", "housed", "It", "in", "the", "Musée", "du", "Louvre", "of", "Paris", "."], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-LOC", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["van", "Paulien", "Jonathans", "Dooremalen", "Lotte"], "ner_tags": ["I-PER", "B-PER", "I-ORG", "I-PER", "B-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Estrela", "Serra", "da", "Subregion"], "ner_tags": ["I-LOC", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["**09621", "Amberg", "(", "Oberpfalz", ")"], "ner_tags": ["O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["East", "Central", "School", "Independent", "District"], "ner_tags": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["''", ":", "B.", ":", ":"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "Jacksons", "(", "TV", "series", ")"], "ner_tags": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER"]}
{"tokens": ["Reagan", "County", ",", "Texas"], "ner_tags": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["Shepard", "H.", "E."], "ner_tags": ["I-PER", "I-PER", "B-PER"]}
{"tokens": ["F.C", "Millonarios", "."], "ner_tags": ["I-ORG", "B-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Communes", "of", "the", "Eure-et", "-Loir", "department"], "ner_tags": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["Ashleigh", ":", "(", "2014", "–", ")", "Brewer"], "ner_tags": ["B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "I-PER"]}
{"tokens": ["Nowinki", ",", "County", "Wołomin"], "ner_tags": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["Lyrics", "Duncan", ")", "Fallowell", "–", "3:30", "/", "5:41", ":"], "ner_tags": ["O", "B-PER", "O", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["*", "Lifetime", "Achievement", "-", "Schlesinger", "Jr", "M.", ",", "Arthur", "."], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "B-PER", "I-PER"]}
{"tokens": ["Hans", "Karl", "Diebitsch", "von"], "ner_tags": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER"]}
{"tokens": ["Crombrugghia", "distans", "''", ",", "1847", "(", "Zeller", ")", "''"], "ner_tags": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Rob", ",", "composer", "Fusari", "–", "producer"], "ner_tags": ["B-PER", "O", "O", "I-PER", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["to", "parents", "of", "origin", "Icelandic", ",", "was", "He", "born", "in", "the", "United", "States", "of", "America", ",", "in", "Hallson", "Dakota", "North", ",", "."], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "I-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["On", "September", "9", ",", "2011", ",", "on", "Slice", "Network", "debuted", "Canada", "Intervention", "''", "."], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "I-ORG", "B-ORG", "O", "O"]}
